whatsgabycooking.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy Policy - What's Gaby Cooking

**Privacy Policy**

Last Updated: June 18, 2018

This Privacy Policy describes how What’s Gaby Cooking, LLC, a Washington limited liability company, and our brands and subsidiaries (“ _Gaby_ ” or “ _us_ ”) collect, use, protect, and share information about you. This policy applies to information we collect when you use our websites, shop in our online stores or otherwise interact with us as described below. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the homepages of our websites or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meanings ascribed thereto in our Terms of Use.

**Acceptance Of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and any changes to this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Collection Of Information**

_Information You Provide to Us_. We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you use our websites, shop in our online stores, call us on the phone, create an online account, sign up to receive our emails, participate in a sweepstakes, contest, promotion or survey, communicate with us via third party social media sites, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, zip code, billing address, shipping address, phone number, payment card information, demographic information and any other information you choose to provide (“Personal Information”). In some cases, we may also collect information you provide about others, such as when you purchase a gift card for someone and request that we deliver it electronically, create and share a “wish list” or decide to purchase and ship products to someone. We will use this information to fulfill your requests and may also use that information to send marketing communications to your contact, unless he or she has previously opted out of marketing communications from Gaby.

_Information We Collect Automatically_. We automatically collect certain information about you when you access or use our websites or transact business with us, including: (i) information about your use of our websites, such as the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the referring link through which you accessed our websites; (ii) information about the transaction, such as product details and the date and location of the purchase/return; and (iii) we may use cookies, web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”) and other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you interact with our websites or emails, including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior. We may combine this information with other information we collect about you and use it for various purposes, such as improving our websites and your online experience, understanding which areas and features of our sites are popular, counting visits, understanding campaign effectiveness, tailoring our communications with you, determining whether an email has been opened and links within the email have been clicked and for other internal business purposes.

_Information We Collect From Our Partners_. We may also obtain information about you from other sources and combine that with information we collect about you. For example, we may collect information from the U.S. Postal Service’s national change of address database to verify and update mailing addresses. 

_Retention and Transfer of Personal Information.   _We retain Personal Information that you provide us as long as we consider it potentially useful in contacting you about our products and services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request by unsubscribing, opting-out, or emailing us at  gaby@whatsgabycooking.com. Personal Information may be transferred and stored to secure servers in the United States.

**Use Of Information**

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to: (i) facilitate and improve your online shopping experience; (ii) provide the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and receipts; (iii) respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service; (iv) communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards and events and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you; (v) manage your online account(s) and send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages; (vi) personalize your online experience and provide advertisements, content or features that match your profile and interests; (vii) monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities; (viii) process and deliver contest, promotion and sweepstakes entries and rewards; (ix) link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and (x) carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.  We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using our websites or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

**Sharing of Information**

We may share information about you as follows: (i) with vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf; (ii) with our business partners and other third parties for purposes of sending their own direct mail; (iii) in response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation; (iv) if we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of us or any third party; (v) in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or transfer of all or a portion of our business to another company; or (vi) with your consent or at your direction. We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you. 

**Advertising and Analytics**

We engage third parties to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of our websites, such as your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our websites and other websites and better understand your online or offline activity. We may also work with third parties to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign on other websites or platforms. 

**Cookies**

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject cookies, but note that doing so does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies used in connection with our websites. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our websites. In addition, many web browsers support Do Not Track technology. If you enable Do Not Track, Gaby will not use information about your web viewing activities to tailor your online experience on other websites operated by Gaby. Note, however, third-party companies may not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals. If you would like to opt out of the collection and use of tracking data for ad targeting, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

**Links To 3** **rd** **Party Websites**

Our Site may contain links to other websites. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of other websites and Gaby is not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our Site and to read the privacy policies of each website that you visit.

**Security**

We take reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.  We use organizational, procedural, and technical safeguards to secure data in our possession, consistent with the sensitivity level of such data. When sensitive information (such as a credit card data) is collected on our Site it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol and may be processed by third parties using similar levels of protection. Regardless of the precautions we take, no transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

**Other Data Protection Rights**

You may have the following data protection rights:

  * To access, correct, update or request deletion of Personal Information. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the data we collect is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and up to date. If you wish to access or delete your Personal Information (if any) you may contact us directly by emailing us at gaby@whatsgabycooking.com or [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com) with respect to advertising on the Site. We will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws. 
  * In addition, individuals who are residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) can object to processing of their Personal Information, ask to restrict processing of their Personal Information or request portability of their Personal Information. You can exercise these rights by contacting us at gaby@whatsgabycooking.com.
  * Similarly, if Personal Information is collected or processed on the basis of consent you can withdraw consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your Personal Information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * EEA residents have the right to complain to a data protection authority about the collection and use of Personal Information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA are available [here](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm).

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection law. We may ask you to verify your identity in order to help us respond efficiently to your request.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. We do not sell products for purchase by children and all children’s products we sell are for purchase by adults only. 

**California Privacy Rights**

California law permits residents of California pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83 to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to gaby@whatsgabycooking.com or write to us at the address in the Contact Section below. Under the law, a business must either provide this information or permit California residents to opt in to, or opt out of, this type of sharing. Gaby permits California residents to opt out of having their information shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. To opt out, please click “unsubscribe” on any emails from us or email us at gaby@whatsgabycooking.com requesting to be removed. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us by email at gaby@whatsgabycooking.com.
